Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/diana-sali (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Public Relations

Media Relations

Strategic Communications

Diana Sali

Senior-Beraterin & Projektleiterin Corporate Communication bei LHLK I #30u30 Crew PR Report 2019
Berlin

Summary

Experienced Senior PR Consultant with a demonstrated history of working in the public relations and communications industry. Skilled in Event Management, Strategic Communications, Social Media as well as Public and Media Relations. Strong media and communication professional with a Master of Arts - MA focused in Communication and Media Studies from Universität Salzburg.

Experience

LHLK

1 year 6 months

Senior Beraterin Corporate Communication January 2022 - Present (3 months) Berlin, Deutschland

Beraterin Corporate Communication October 2020 - January 2022 (1 year 4 months) Berlin, Deutschland

Red Lorry Yellow Lorry
2 years 6 months
Senior Account Executive
January 2019 - October 2020 (1 year 10 months)
Berlin

Junior PR Consultant May 2018 - January 2019 (9 months)

Plenos - Agentur für Kommunikation 1 year PR Trainee September 2016 - February 2017 (6 months) Salzburg

PR Intern

March 2016 - August 2016 (6 months)

Salzburg

FlixBus

Marketing Intern

April 2015 - June 2015 (3 months)

Munich Area, Germany

BMW Group

Corporate Communications Intern

August 2014 - February 2015 (7 months)

Regensburg Area, Germany

Gong Verlag GmbH

Intern

August 2011 - September 2011 (2 months)

Munich Area, Germany

Eurofighter Jagdflugzeug GmbH

Intern

July 2008 - August 2008 (2 months)

Munich Area, Germany

Education

Universität Salzburg

Master of Arts - MA, Communication and Media Studies · (2015 - 2018)

Otto-Friedrich-Universität Bamberg

Bachelor of Arts - BA, Communication and Media Studies · (2011 - 2015)

Otto-Friedrich-Universität Bamberg

Bachelor of Arts - BA, German Language and Literature · (2011 - 2015)